What are the benefits of tutoring?
The benefits of tutoring are for... Well, okay.
There's the benefit to the student getting to learn things, and then there's the benefit to the tutor getting to make a living.
But also, as opposed to any other job, let's say, the tutor gets to make his own hours a little bit more than most other people.
So there's easier scheduling.
There is easier scheduling.
There is a decent pay, usually.
A lot of times, if there's a middle man involved, your pay cut is pretty steep, but then your middle man is getting you...getting you clients, so that's a trade-off that you have to make sometimes.
It's also a pretty fun job if you like explaining things and it makes you feel smart.
There's also the ego boost of having your...having your paradigm -- your thought pattern -- you know, put out into the world and adopted by somebody else.
That's a pretty big responsibility, though, so you have to make sure that you...you know, that it...that it makes sense -- that it's pretty water-tight.
That is the benefit to tutoring as a job.